<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Angel Guarisma on </title>
    <link>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Angel Guarisma on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to SELinux</title>
      <link>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/selinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/selinux/</guid>
      <description>SELinux is a Mandatory Access Control (MAC) system, developed by the NSA. SELinux was developed as a replacement for Discretionary Access Control (DAC) that ships with most Linux distributions.
The difference between Discretionary Access Controls and Mandatory Access Controls is the means by which users and applications gain access to machines. Traditionally, the command sudo gives a user the ability to heighten permissions to root-level. Root access on a DAC system gives the person or program with root access permission to perform as desired on a machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Postfix Issues</title>
      <link>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/troubleshooting-postfix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/troubleshooting-postfix/</guid>
      <description>Because setting up a mail server is tricky, we&amp;rsquo;ve created this companion troubleshooting guide to help you work through and resolve any problems you might be experiencing. By the time you reach the end of this guide, you&amp;rsquo;ll know how to debug problems with your Postfix, Dovecot, and MySQL mail server.
The first section, Troubleshooting Checklist, has a top-down approach to troubleshooting that will help you find specific errors for your mail server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Turtl on Linux</title>
      <link>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/turtl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/turtl/</guid>
      <description>What is Turtl? Turtl is an open-source alternative to cloud-based storage services. With a focus on privacy, Turtl offers a place to store and access your passwords, bookmarks and pictures. Hosting your own Turtl server on a secure server allows you to monitor your own security.
The Turtl server is written in Common Lisp, and the low-level encryption is derived from the Stanford JavaScript Crypto Library. If encryption is important to you, read over the encryption specifics section of the official documentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Redmine</title>
      <link>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/redmine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guaris.github.io/portfolio/redmine/</guid>
      <description>What is Redmine? Redmine is a project management web app that allows users to manage projects flexibly while offering robust tracking tools and an extensive library of plug-ins. This free and open source solution offers an alternative to paid project management tools and includes support for wikis, forums, calendars, and data visualization tools.
This guide will show you how to install and set up Redmine on Ubuntu 16.04 through the Passenger application server connected to NGINX.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>